guys so this is a pretty legit calculus
challenge it uses very basic derivative
skills but it can be very tricky if
you're not careful if you want to try it
out pause it right now because I'm going
to give the answer in three two one what
it's asking for is the double derivative
of f of x to the four so I'm going to
put the derivative of derivative of f of
x to the fourth so we're going to solve
this inside first so this up here says
the derivative of f of x is G of X so
this is just going to be G of whatever
is inside here G of x to the fourth and
then we have to take the chain rule of
whatever's inside here so we're going to
multiply this by the derivative of
what's inside here which is 4X cubed our
first step is now done now we gotta take
the derivative of what's inside here
unfortunately it is a product of two
functions so we have to use the product
rule so we're going to do the derivative
of this first function and leave the
second function alone plus the
derivative of the second function
multiplied by the first function left
alone so this derivative of GX to the
fourth so it says the derivative of G of
X is f of x cubed so the derivative of G
of x to the fourth would be f of x to
the fourth Cube so then because is the
chain rule we have to multiply it by the
derivative of this inner function x to
the fourth which gives us 4X cubed and
then we're going to multiply by this
other 4X cubed plus the derivative of
this is just 12x squared and then this
GX to the 4 is just left alone we can
clean things up 4 times 4 is 16 x cubed
times x cubed is X to the sixth and then
bring this down and x to the fourth to
the third is X to the 12th plus and this
term can't really simplify so there it
is right there and that is the answer to
the question how exciting is that what
you got